Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Take a breath
休息一下
Imagine
想象
The bright blue sky beyond the clouds
那朵雲之外湛藍的天空
那朵云之外湛蓝的天空
彼|<か方|な#|た先|<さ#|きの最|<さい盛|せ#|いの景|<け色|し#|きを
The most wonderful sight over the horizon
那遙遠的彼方最美的景色
那遥远的彼方最美的景色
ka na ta sa ki no sa i se i no ke shi ki o
解|<ほ#|#|どかれてく 憂|<う#|れいのすべて 綻|<ほ#|#|こ#|#|ろびだす 想|<お#|もいたちよ
The worries ebb and the thoughts flow
逐漸解開 種種憂愁 逐漸綻放 縷縷思緒
逐渐解开 种种忧愁 逐渐绽放 缕缕思绪
ho do ka re te ku u re i no su be te ho ko ro bi da su o mo i ta chi yo
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
暗|<く#|ら闇|や#|みに朝|<あ#|さ日|ひが咲|<さいてゆくように
Like the sun rising in the dark
彷彿在黑暗中綻放的朝陽
彷佛在黑暗中绽放的朝阳
ku ra ya mi ni a sa hi ga sa i te yu ku yo u ni
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
閉|<とじていたその目|<めに希|<き望|ぼ#|うを映|<う#|つそう
Awaken your closed eyes with hope
讓曾閉上的雙眸中重新閃爍希望
让曾闭上的双眸中重新闪烁希望
to ji te i ta so no me ni ki bo u o u tsu so u
Fly away, far away
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
どこまでも自|<じ由|ゆ#|うに舞|<まう羽|<は#|ねのように
Like the free wings that roam sky
宛如可以到處自由飛翔的羽翼
宛如可以到处自由飞翔的羽翼
do ko ma de mo ji yu u ni ma u ha ne no yo u ni
Fly away, far away
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
高|<た#|か鳴|<なりのはじまりへ 心|<こ#|こ#|ろ共|<ど#|もに行|<いこう
Follow the beckoning of your heart
迴歸心動的初始 隨心同行
回归心动的初始 随心同行
ta ka na ri no ha ji ma ri e ko ko ro do mo ni i ko u
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Can you feel, a changing wind?
你能感受到風向正在改變嗎？
你能感受到风向正在改变吗？
Everything may be alright
一切都會好起來的
一切都会好起来的
やがて来|<き#|たる快|<かい晴|せ#|いを望|<の#|ぞんで
Believe the sun will soon shine again
盼望著即將到來的晴天
盼望着即将到来的晴天
ya ga te ki ta ru ka i se i o no zon de
頬|<ほ#|#|おを撫|<なでる 優|<や#|さしきすべて 恐|<お#|#|それさえも 包|<つ#|つむように
The kindness that gently touches you and conquer fear
輕撫臉頰 種種善良 即使是恐懼 也能被包容
轻抚脸颊 种种善良 即使是恐惧 也能被包容
ho o o na de ru ya sa shi ki su be te o so re sa e mo tsu tsu mu yo u ni
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
爪|<つ#|ま先|さ#|きで打|<うち鳴|<ならすリ|<rhyズ|thム|mに乗|<のるように
Like the rhythm drummed by your fingers
就像跟著你指尖敲出的節奏
就像跟着你指尖敲出的节奏
tsu ma sa ki de u chi na ra su ri zu mu ni no ru yo u ni
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
その心|<こ#|こ#|ろ軽|<か#|ろやかに明|<あ日|すを迎|<む#|かえに行|<いこう
Embrace a new day with an easy heart
你的心將輕鬆地迎接明天的到來
你的心将轻松地迎接明天的到来
so no ko ko ro ka ro ya ka ni a su o mu ka e ni i ko u
Still believe...
依然相信
思|<お#|もい出|<だす彼|<かれの日|<ひを全|<す#|べて 変|<かわる前|<ま#|えの世|<せ界|か#|いを
Reminiscing about what the world once was
會想起當年 一切都還未變化的世界
会想起当年 一切都还未变化的世界
o mo i da su ka re no hi o su be te ka wa ru ma e no se ka i o
Still blowing...
微風依舊
微风依旧
風|<か#|ぜに吹|<ふかれながら 巡|<め#|ぐる空|<そ#|らの向|<むこう想|<お#|もう
Longing for the same place beneath the sky
清風吹過 想念著同一片天空的彼方
清风吹过 想念着同一片天空的彼方
ka ze ni fu ka re na ga ra me gu ru so ra no mu ko u o mo u
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
暗|<く#|ら闇|や#|みに朝|<あ#|さ日|ひが咲|<さいてゆくように
Like the sun rising in the dark
彷彿在黑暗中綻放的朝陽
彷佛在黑暗中绽放的朝阳
ku ra ya mi ni a sa hi ga sa i te yu ku yo u ni
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
閉|<とじていたその目|<めに希|<き望|ぼ#|うを映|<う#|つそう
Awaken your closed eyes with hope
讓曾閉上的雙眸中重新閃爍希望
让曾闭上的双眸中重新闪烁希望
to ji te i ta so no me ni ki bo u o u tsu so u
Fly away, far away
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
どこまでも自|<じ由|ゆ#|うに舞|<まう羽|<は#|ねのように
Like the free wings that roam sky
宛如可以到處自由飛翔的羽翼
宛如可以到处自由飞翔的羽翼
do ko ma de mo ji yu u ni ma u ha ne no yo u ni
Fly away, far away
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
高|<た#|か鳴|<なりのはじまりへ 心|<こ#|こ#|ろ共|<ど#|もに行|<いこう
Follow the beckoning of your heart
迴歸心動的初始 隨心同行
回归心动的初始 随心同行
ka ta na ri no ha ji ma ri e ko ko ro do mo ni i ko u
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Go on.
繼續前進吧
继续前进吧
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Everything will be alright
一切都會好起來的
一切都会好起来的
Shine a light on your life...
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光
Just carry on
堅持下去
坚持下去
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
A bright future is awaiting you
美好的未來正等著你
美好的未来正等着你
Fly away, far away...
飛翔吧向著遠方
飞翔吧向着远方
Shine a light on your life
給你的生命一束光
给你的生命一束光